// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1 Joule=-_________engs",
    answer: "10⁷",
    options: [
      "10⁷",
      "10–⁷",
      "4.2",
      "2.4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Dimensional formulae of force is______?",
      answer: "MLT–²",
    options: [
      "ML–²T–²",
      "MLT–¹",
      "MLT–²",
      "ML–¹T–²"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Select the scalar quantity?",
    answer: "Pressure",
    options: [
      "Force",
      "Velocity",
      "Acceleration",
      "Pressure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a vector?",
    answer: "Velocity",
    options: [
      "Time",
      "Volume",
      "Speed",
      "Velocity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Dimensional formulae of acceleration is_________",
    answer: "M°LT-²",
    options: [
      "M°LT–²",
      "M°L¹T–²",
      "MLT–³",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Velocity of C.G.S unity is?",
    answer: "cm/s",
    options: [
      "cm/s²",
      "cm/s",
      "cm²/s2",
      "cm³/s"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The force which opposses relative motion and the bodies is called______",
    answer: "Friction",
    options: [
      "Friction",
      "Angular momentum",
      "Velocity",
      "None of these"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Formulae of velocity",
    answer: "displacement/time",
    options: [
      "displacement/time",
      "volume/displacement",
      "time/displacement",
      "None of these "
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The vcelocity of the particle at any instant of time is?",
      answer: "Instantaneous velocity",
    options: [
      "Volume",
      "Instantaneous velocity",
      "Displacement",
      "Momentum"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Body of mass 0.987kg is suspended from a spring of spring constant k=2N/M,then the time period is__________",
    answer: "4.4sec",
    options: [
      "4.9sec",
      "4.4sec",
      "4.8sec",
      "4.2sec"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The Maximum speed of a body travelling under SHM with a time period of π/4 sec and amplitude of 7cm is ",
    answer: "56cm/s",
    options: [
      "58cm/s",
      "56cm/s",
      "69cm/s",
      "72cm/s"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 12,
    question: "which of the following Uses the phenomenon of echoes",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Stethoscope",
      "Megaptone",
      "Sonar",
      "All the above"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 13,
    question: "A Sound Wave is a_____",
    answer: "Longitudinal Mechanical Wave",
    options: [
      "Transversal Mechanical Wave",
      "Longitudinal Mechanical Wave",
      "Longitudinal Electromagnetic Wave",
      "Transverse Electromagnetic Wave"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Find the length of the Second's pendulum at a place where g=9.8 m/s.....",
    answer: "0.992 cm",
    options: [
      "0.996 cm",
      "0.992 cm",
      "0.972 cm",
      "None Of These"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The problem of echelon effect can be removed by cuống",
    answer: "Stair Carpet",
    options: [
      "Iron board",
      "Stair Carpet",
      "Multiple doors& Windows",
      "Wooden Boards"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 16,
    question: "The intensity of threshold of pain is",
    answer: "120dB",
    options: [
      "12dB",
      "120bel",
      "120dB",
      "0dB"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Sound Can't travel through?",
    answer: "Vaccum",
    options: [
      "Solids",
      "Liquids",
      "Gases",
      "Vaccum"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 18,
    question: "A cinema hall has a Volume of 8000m³.It is required to have the reverberation time of 1.5 Seconds. The total Obsorptionin in the hall is",
    answer: "880",
    options: [
      "440",
      "880",
      "1980",
      "72.72"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The amount of work to be done for producing 500 calories of heat is",
    answer: "2100 Joules",
    options: [
      "500 ergs",
      "500 Joules",
      "21,000 ergs",
      "2100 Joules"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The Internal Energy of an ideal gas depends only opon",
    answer: "Temparature",
    options: [
      "Pressure",
      "Volume",
      "Temparature",
      "Size of the Molecules"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 21,
    question: "The length of a Second's penduleun is 100cm. To have a period fhalf of this Valve the length is to reduced by______",
    answer: "75cm",
    options: [
      "25cm",
      "75cm",
      "50cm",
      "100cm"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Adiabatic Relation between Pressure and Volume",
    answer: "pv=constant",
    options: [
      "pv=constant",
      "Pv=Rt",
      "pr^y=constant",
      "p^yv=constant"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 23,
    question: "dQ=dW and du= is true for",
    answer: "Isochoric process",
    options: [
      "Isothermal",
      "Adiabatic process",
      "Isoboric process",
      "Isochoric process"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 24,
    question: "The work function is less for",
    answer: "Al",
    options: [
      "Cu",
      "Ag",
      "Al",
      "Ce"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 25,
    question: "One kilo-watt hour is",
    answer: "36x10 Joules",
    options: [
      "36 Joules",
      "36x10³ Joules",
      "36x10⁴ Joules",
      "36x10⁵ Joules"
    ]
  },
  
];